cokeandpopcorn.ch 2015-12-06

# Coke & Popcorn > Privacy Policy

###  Privacy Policy

We take the privacy of our users very seriously. Here we explain in detail what information we collect from you and how we use that information. We reserve the right to change this policy at any time, please check this page periodically to learn about any new changes.

**1\. Personal Information**  
When trying to post comments, you may have to provide some personal information about yourself, such as your name and email. You can also add an avatar (personal image) or build a profile to share with our other users. Our comment plugin system is powered by DISQUS, please visit their site to learn more about their terms We will not share your email with any third party. We will use your email to send notifications to you. We may send a cookie to your browser so our comment system can remember you and make posting comments easier in the future.

**2\. Statistical (Non-personal) Information**  
We often collect non-personal information to help us serve our users better. This includes things like your browser, operating system, ISP etc. This information is used by us for making cokeandpopcorn.ch more compatible and user-friendly for you.

**3\. Third Party Content**  
cokeandpopcorn.ch contains many links to other websites. Many of these links are posted by our users and we have no control over the content on these third party websites. 

**4\. Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).   
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated infromation (not including your name, address, emal address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp
